

With expertise in corporate communications, I am dedicated to crafting strategic campaigns that enhance internal engagement and brand reputation. My experience in public relations, content creation, and event coordination allows me to assist managing the company's effective internal communication strategies.

My goal is to become a leading internal communication expert, helping businesses strengthen their brand and achieve sustainable growth.

Contact

- thy.tranvothimai@gmail.com
- 0939619095
- https://thytvtm.my.canva.site/
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/thytran2706/

Education

Business English and Corporate Communications Hoa Sen University GPA: 3.37/4

Key areas: Internal Communication, Corporate Communication Strategy, Essentials Skills for PR, Fundamental of Marketing & Sales, Customer Service & Relations Management, etc

Skills

Graphic design)

Microsoft Office

Writing & Editing

Solution oriented (Time management)

Research & data driven (Adaptable and problem-solving

Certificates

TOEIC: 810/990

Marketing certificates: Fundamentals of digital marketing (Google Online Course)

Sustainability/CSR certificates:

- Enhancing Business Capacity to Adapt to Green Transition, Emission Reduction & Greenhouse Gas Inventory Practice (Ministry of Planning and Investment & USAID)
- CSRD Fundamentals Certifications (CSRD Institute)
- Impact Measurement & Management for the SDGs (Coursera & Duke University)

References

Mr. Triệu Thanh Thinh (Thinh Trieu) Công ty Cổ phần Đầu tư Thế Giới Di Động ESG Manager

Mobile: (+84) 932190792

Email: thinh.trieuthanh@thegioididong.com

Trần Võ Thị Mai Thy

Employee Engagement & Internal Communication Staff

Work experiences

SUSTAINABILITY INTERN

03/2024 - 09/2024

CÔNG TY CỔ PHẦN ĐẦU TƯ THẾ GIỚI DI ĐÔNG

1. Corporate Communication (60%)

Internal Communications

- Created internal newsletters, internal communication materials to align corporate messaging.
- Assisted in executing internal events to raise ESG awareness and employee
- Assisted in planning ideas and executing engagement programs to retain valuable employees
- o Produced internal E-learning courses on Environment & Society to encourage employee's learning & development activities.

External Communications

- Assisted in managing corporate reputation, handling crisis communication, and responding to media inquiries.
- Gathered data for corporate award applications.

CSR Event Implementation

- o Collaborate with stakeholders and cross-functional internal teams to organize and facilitate ESG/CSR initiatives that enhance corporate reputation.
- Implemented communication plans for CSR campaigns.

• Design ESG communication materials: posters, propaganda videos, infographics, etc

2. Sustainability (40%)

Internal Policy Development & ESG Research

- Research and develop trends, standards, and policies related to ESG.
- Proposed and developed policies to improve the working environment for employees, including: Code of Conduct, Human Rights Policy, Reducing Gender Pay Gap, etc.
- Collect and analyze sustainability performance data to assess impact and

· Sustainability Reporting & Compliance:

• Assist in preparing sustainability reports, ESG disclosures, and corporate responsibility statements.

COMMUNICATIONS AND MARKETING OFFICER

07/2022 - 01/2023

ATC WINE MERCHANTS

1. Branding communication

- Content Creation: Develop daily content for Facebook, Instagram, and TikTok to promote sustainability products.
- Campaign Development: Developed multimedia advertising campaigns for target customer, enhancing brand awareness through seasonal campaigns like Christmas and New Year.
- TikTok Series Productions: Created content series on Facebook & Instagram.
- Event & Brand Promotion: Support events organization and brand promotion to enhance product visibility and media exposure.
- Brand Consistency & Local Relevance: Work with marketing team to ensure brand alignment and cultural sensitivity
- Graphic Design: Design communication materials: catalogs, videos, POSM, etc.

2. Assistant in planning

Market Research: Research marketing trends based on international & domestic standards, and assist in proposing integrating the IMC model into marketing and customer care plans.

CONTENT CREATION CONTRIBUTOR

07/2017 - 03/2019

150486 - 나, 너, 우리

1. Social media communication:

- Content Creation: Curate, translate, and edit trending news from English sources; and develop daily content (7 posts/week) to boost user engagement.
- **Graphic Design**: Collaborate with the design team to create visual content.
- 2. Event organization:
 - External event: Plan, coordinate and implement initiative in the event.